export const questions = [
  {
    "category": "Ifulfill 1",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        "question": "<p>question 1?</p>",
        "answer": "Answer 1"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        "question": "<p>question 2?</p>",
        "answer": "Answer 2"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        "question": "<p>question 3?</p>",
        "answer": "Answer 3"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        "question": "<p>question 4?</p>",
        "answer": "Answer 4"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Ifulfill 2",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        "question": "<p>question 1?</p>",
        "answer": "Answer 1"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        "question": "<p>question 2?</p>",
        "answer": "Answer 2"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        "question": "<p>question 3?</p>",
        "answer": "Answer 3"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        "question": "<p>question 4?</p>",
        "answer": "Answer 4"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Ifulfill 3",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        "question": "<p>question 1?</p>",
        "answer": "Answer 1"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        "question": "<p>question 2?</p>",
        "answer": "Answer 2"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        "question": "<p>question 3?</p>",
        "answer": "Answer 3"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        "question": "<p>question 4?</p>",
        "answer": "Answer 4"
      }
    ]
  }
];